homepageseek.com 2006-06-30

# Homepageseek Privacy Statement

## _Privacy Statement for HomepageSeek_

HomepageSeek has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: HomepageSeek. 

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

Cookies are used to keep track of your shopping cart at HomepageSeek Electronics, HomepageSeek Gifts, and HomepageSeek Sporting Goods. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. 

Our site's registration and e-zine form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

This site contains links to other sites. **HomepageSeek** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

HomepageSeek Electronics, HomepageSeek Gifts, and HomepageSeek Sporting Goods uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. VStore.com is the fulfillment center and they collect visitor's contact information (like their e-mail address). Users may view their policies at: 

   1.   [Privacy](http://vstore.vstoremarket.com/helppopup.htm?tab=policies&file=help_safe_shop.jsp)

   2.   [Security](http://vstore.vstoremarket.com/helppopup.htm?tab=policies&file=help_safe_shop.jsp)

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control   Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, HomepageSeek cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at any time.. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database, to not receive future communications, or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [optout@homepageseek.com](mailto:webmaster@homepageseek.com)
  2. You can send email to: [webmaster@homepageseek.com](mailto:webmaster@homepageseek.com)  

If you believe you have been spammed please contact us for immediate action at the following:

  1. You can send email to [abuse@homepageseek.com](mailto:webmaster@homepageseek.com)

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [update@homepageseek.com](mailto:webmaster@homepageseek.com)
  2. visit <http://www.homepageseek/addurl.htm>

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:        1.   email  [privacy@homepageseek.com](mailto:privacy@homepageseek.com)
